

SANTIAGO J. CRIPPA

FRONT END DEVELOPER

I am a technology enthusiast with a passion for front-end programming and design. I believe in technology's transformative power to enhance lives. Professionally, I aim to leverage my skills to craft exceptional digital experiences and contribute to a sustainable, environmentally conscious future.

11-3146-6075



santicrippa@gmail.com



Wilde, Buenos Aires, Argentina



www.linkedin.com/in/santiago-julian-crippa

SOFT SKILLS

- Strong Communication
- Team work
- Problem-Solving
- Creativity
- Adaptability
- Critical thinking
- · Decision making
- Time management

EDUCATION

HIGH SCHOOL

San Ignacio School. 200<u>2 - 2015</u>

COLLEGE'S

National Technological University (UTN) *Electronic Engineering. 2016 - 2018*

National University of Arts. (UNA) Audiovisual production. 2019 - 2022

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CoderHouse Academy. 2022 - Actually

LANGUAGES

English: Bilingual. Spanish: Native.

CODING KNOWLEDGE

LENGUAGES, FRAMEWORKS AND MORE

- Web design (HTML CSS Responsive Design)
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React JS
- Next JS
- React Native
- Redux
- Expo
- SCSS SASS
- Git GitHub
- Firebase Firestore
- Test-Drive-Development (Vitest)

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE DEVELOPER

March 2023 - December 2023

- Database administration, website and mobile design, using figma and more.
- Building a video-call mobile app using React Native,
 Expo and Clerck for auth.

LIVE SUBASTAS APPLICATION

December 2023 - Actually

- Using React, TypeScript, Redux and more.
- Application diagnosis, tracking bugs, bad practices and performance.
- · Repair, cleanup and refactoring process.
- Development of functionalities and features.